{"country":[
	{"code":"SE-O","name":"Västra Götaland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"15"},
	{"code":"SE-N","name":"Halland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"9"},
	{"code":"SE-M","name":"Skåne","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"5"},
	{"code":"SE-K","name":"Blekinge","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"4"},
	{"code":"SE-I","name":"Gotland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"2"},
	{"code":"SE-H","name":"Kalmar","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"2"},
	{"code":"SE-G","name":"Kronoberg","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"8"},
	{"code":"SE-F","name":"Jönköping","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"9"},
	{"code":"SE-E","name":"Östergötland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"1"},
	{"code":"SE-D","name":"Södermanland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"2"},
	{"code":"SE-C","name":"Uppsala","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"6"},
	{"code":"SE-W","name":"Dalarna","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"3"},
	{"code":"SE-Z","name":"Jämtland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"2"},
	{"code":"SE-Y","name":"Västernorrland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"1"},
	{"code":"SE-X","name":"Gävleborg","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"22"},
	{"code":"SE-AC","name":"Västerbotten","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"44"},
	{"code":"SE-AB","name":"Stockholm","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"2"},
	{"code":"SE-U","name":"Västmanland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"9"},
	{"code":"SE-T","name":"Orebro","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"1"},
	{"code":"SE-S","name":"Värmland","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"100"},
	{"code":"SE-BD","name":"Norrbotten","question":"Why?","answer":".","points":"34"}
]}